<document id="document-1"><clause id="clause-1" level="1" numbering="1."><content>THIS BANK GUARANTEE AGREEMENT executed at _________this _________day of _________201 by _________ (Name of the Bank) _________ having its Registered Office at _________and its Branch at _________ (hereinafter referred to as "the Guarantor", which expression shall, unless it be repugnant to the subject, meaning or context thereof, be deemed to mean and include its successors and permitted assigns) IN FAVOUR OF State Bank of India, a Statutory Corporation constituted under the State Bank of India Act, 1955 having its Corporate Centre at State Bank Bhavan, Nariman Point, Mumbai and one of its offices at____________(procuring office address), hereinafter referred to as "SBI" which expression shall, unless repugnant to the subject, context or meaning thereof, be deemed to mean and include its successors and assigns).</content></clause><clause id="clause-2" level="1" numbering="2."><content>WHEREAS M/s__________________________________________, incorporated under __________________________________ Act having its registered office at __________________________________ and principal place of business at __________________________________ (hereinafter referred to as “Service Provider/ Vendor” which expression shall unless repugnant to the context or meaning thereof shall include its successor, executor &amp; assigns) has agreed to develop, implement and support _________ (name of  Service) (hereinafter referred to as “Services”) to SBI in accordance with the Request for Proposal (RFP) No. SBI:xx:xx dated dd/mm/yyyy.</content></clause><clause id="clause-3" level="1" numbering="3."><content>WHEREAS, SBI has agreed to avail the Services from Service Provider for a period of ______ year(s) subject to the terms and conditions mentioned in the RFP.</content></clause><clause id="clause-4" level="1" numbering="4."><content>WHEREAS, in accordance with terms and conditions of the RFP/Purchase order/Agreement dated_________, Service Provider is required to furnish a Bank Guarantee for a sum of Rs.__________/- (Rupees _________ only) for due performance of the obligations of Service Provider in providing the Services, in accordance with the RFP/Purchase order/Agreement guaranteeing payment of the said amount of Rs.__________/- (Rupees __________ only) to SBI, if Service Provider fails to fulfill its obligations as agreed in RFP/Agreement.</content></clause><clause id="clause-5" level="1" numbering="5."><content>WHEREAS, the Bank Guarantee is required to be valid for a total period of _____ months and in the event of failure, on the part of Service Provider, to fulfill any of its commitments / obligations under the RFP/Agreement, SBI shall be entitled to invoke the Guarantee. AND WHEREAS, the Guarantor, at the request of Service Provider, agreed to issue, on behalf of Service Provider, Guarantee as above, for an amount of Rs.___________/- (Rupees ___________ only). NOW THIS GUARANTEE WITNESSETH THAT</content><clause id="clause-6" level="2" numbering="1."><content>In consideration of SBI having agreed to entrust Service Provider for rendering Services as mentioned in the RFP, we,  the Guarantors, hereby unconditionally and irrevocably guarantee that Service Provider shall fulfill its commitments and obligations in respect of providing the Services as mentioned in the RFP/Agreement and in the event of Service Provider failing to perform / fulfill its commitments / obligations in respect of providing Services as mentioned in the RFP/Agreement, we (the Guarantor) shall on demand(s), from time to time from SBI, without protest or demur or without reference to Service Provider and not withstanding any contestation or existence of any dispute whatsoever between Service Provider and SBI, pay SBI forthwith the sums so demanded by SBI not exceeding Rs.__________/- (Rupees ____________only).</content></clause><clause id="clause-7" level="2" numbering="2."><content>Any notice / communication / demand from SBI to the effect that Service Provider has failed to fulfill its commitments / obligations in respect of rendering the Services as mentioned in the Agreement, shall be conclusive, final &amp; binding on the Guarantor and shall not be questioned by the Guarantor in or outside the court, tribunal, authority or arbitration as the case may be and all such demands shall be honoured by the Guarantor without any delay.</content></clause><clause id="clause-8" level="2" numbering="3."><content>We (the Guarantor) confirm that our obligation to the SBI, under this Guarantee shall be independent of the agreement or other understandings, whatsoever, between the SBI and Service Provider.</content></clause><clause id="clause-9" level="2" numbering="4."><content>This Guarantee shall not be revoked by us (the Guarantor) without prior consent in writing of the SBI. WE (THE GUARANTOR) HEREBY FURTHER AGREE &amp; DECLARE THAT- i. Any neglect or forbearance on the part of SBI to Service Provider or any indulgence of any kind shown by SBI to Service Provider or any change in the terms and conditions of the Agreement or the Services shall not, in any way, release or discharge the Bank from its liabilities under this Guarantee. ii. This Guarantee herein contained shall be distinct and independent and shall be enforceable against the Guarantor, notwithstanding any Guarantee or Security now or hereinafter held by SBI at its discretion. iii. This Guarantee shall not be affected by any infirmity or absence or irregularity in the execution of this Guarantee by and / or on behalf of the Guarantor or by merger or amalgamation or any change in the Constitution or name of the Guarantor. iv. The Guarantee shall not be affected by any change in the constitution of SBI or Service Provider or winding up / liquidation of Service Provider, whether voluntary or otherwise v. This Guarantee shall be a continuing guarantee during its validity period. vi. This Guarantee shall remain in full force and effect for a period of __ year(s) _____ month(s) from the date of the issuance i.e. up to _________. Unless a claim under this Guarantee is made against us on or before _____ , all your rights under this Guarantee shall be forfeited and we shall be relieved and discharged from all liabilities there under. vii. This Guarantee shall be governed by Indian Laws and the Courts in Mumbai, India alone shall have the jurisdiction to try &amp; entertain any dispute arising out of this Guarantee. Notwithstanding anything contained herein above: i. Our liability under this Bank Guarantee shall not exceed Rs__________________/- (Rs. ________________only) ii. This Bank Guarantee shall be valid upto________________ iii. We are liable to pay the guaranteed amount or any part thereof under this Bank Guarantee only and only if SBI serve upon us a written claim or demand on or before ________________ Yours faithfully, For and on behalf of bank. __________________________ Authorised official FORMAT FOR EMD BANK GUARANTEE To: ------------------- ------------------- EMD BANK GUARANTEE FOR NAME OF SERVICES TO STATE BANK OF INDIA TO MEET SUCH REQUIRMENT AND PROVIDE SUCH SERVICES AS ARE SET OUT IN THE RFP NO.SBI:xx:xx DATED dd/mm/yyyy WHEREAS State Bank of India (SBI), having its Corporate Office at Nariman Point, Mumbai, and Regional offices at other State capital cities in India has invited Request to provide ________________(name of Service) as are set out in the  Request for Proposal SBI:xx:xx dated dd/mm/yyyy.</content><clause id="clause-10" level="3" numbering="2."><content>It is one of the terms of said Request for Proposal that the Bidder shall furnish a Bank Guarantee for a sum of Rs._________/-(Rupees _____________________ only) as Earnest Money Deposit.</content></clause><clause id="clause-11" level="3" numbering="3."><content>M/s. ________________________, (hereinafter called as Bidder, who are our constituents intends to submit their Bid for the said work and have requested us to furnish guarantee in respect of the said sum of Rs.__________/-(Rupees _____________________ only)</content></clause><clause id="clause-12" level="3" numbering="4."><content>NOW THIS GUARANTEE WITNESSETH THAT We _____________________________ (Bank) do hereby agree with and undertake to the State Bank of India, their Successors, assigns that in the event of the SBI coming to the conclusion that the Bidder has not performed their obligations under the said conditions of the RFP or have committed a breach thereof, which conclusion shall be binding on us as well as the said Bidder, we shall on demand by the SBI, pay without demur to the SBI, a sum of Rs.__________/-  (Rupees _____________________ Only)  that may be demanded by SBI. Our guarantee shall be treated as equivalent to the Earnest Money Deposit for the due performance of the obligations of the Bidder under the said conditions, provided, however, that our liability against such sum shall not exceed the sum of Rs.__________/-  (Rupees _____________________ Only).</content></clause></clause><clause id="clause-13" level="2" numbering="5."><content>We also agree to undertake to and confirm that the sum not exceeding Rs.__________/- (Rupees _____________________ Only) as aforesaid shall be paid by us without any demur or protest, merely on demand from the SBI on receipt of a notice in writing stating the amount is due to them and we shall not ask for any further proof or evidence and the notice from the SBI shall be conclusive and binding on us and shall not be questioned by us in any respect or manner whatsoever. We undertake to pay the amount claimed by the SBI, without protest or demur or without reference to Bidder and not-withstanding any contestation or existence of any dispute whatsoever between Bidder and SBI, pay SBI forthwith from the date of receipt of the notice as aforesaid. We confirm that our obligation to the SBI under this guarantee shall be independent of the agreement or agreements or other understandings between the SBI and the Bidder. This guarantee shall not be revoked by us without prior consent in writing of the SBI.</content></clause></clause><clause id="clause-14" level="1" numbering="6."><content>We hereby further agree that –</content><clause id="clause-15" level="2" numbering="a)"><content>Any forbearance or commission on the part of the SBI in enforcing the conditions of the said agreement or in compliance with any of the terms and conditions stipulated in the said Bid and/or hereunder or granting of any time or showing of any indulgence by the SBI to the Bidder or any other matter in connection therewith shall not discharge us in any way our obligation under this guarantee. This guarantee shall be discharged only by the performance of  the Bidder of their obligations and in the event of their failure to do so, by payment by us of the sum not exceeding Rs.__________/-  (Rupees _____________________ Only)</content></clause><clause id="clause-16" level="2" numbering="b)"><content>Our liability under these presents shall not exceed the sum of Rs.__________/- (Rupees _____________________ Only)</content><clause id="clause-17" level="3" numbering="c)"><content>Our liability under this agreement shall not be affected by any infirmity or irregularity on the part of our said constituents in tendering for the said work or their obligations there under or by dissolution or change in the constitution of our said constituents.</content><clause id="clause-18" level="4" numbering="d)"><content>This guarantee shall remain in force upto 180 days provided that if so desired by the SBI, this guarantee shall be renewed for a further period as may be indicated by them on the same terms and conditions as contained herein.</content><clause id="clause-19" level="5" numbering="e)"><content>Our liability under this presents will terminate unless these presents are renewed as provided herein upto 180 days or on the day when our said constituents comply with their obligations, as to which a certificate in writing by the SBI alone is the conclusive proof, whichever date is earlier.</content></clause><clause id="clause-20" level="5" numbering="f)"><content>Unless a claim or suit or action is filed against us on or before____(date to be filled by BG issuing bank), all the rights of the SBI against us under this guarantee shall be forfeited and we shall be released and discharged from all our obligations and liabilities hereunder.</content></clause><clause id="clause-21" level="5" numbering="g)"><content>This guarantee shall be governed by Indian Laws and the Courts in Mumbai, India alone shall have the jurisdiction to try &amp; entertain any dispute arising out of this guarantee. Notwithstanding anything contained hereinabove:</content><clause id="clause-22" level="6" numbering="(a)"><content>Our liability under this Bank Guarantee shall not exceed Rs……….………/- (Rupees …………………….only)</content></clause><clause id="clause-23" level="6" numbering="(b)"><content>This Bank Guarantee shall be valid upto ……………………….</content></clause><clause id="clause-24" level="6" numbering="(c)"><content>We are liable to pay the guaranteed amount or any part thereof under this Bank Guarantee only and only if you serve upon us a written claim or demand on or before …………………… Yours faithfully, For and on behalf of _______________________________ Authorized official of the bank (Note: This guarantee will require stamp duty as applicable in the State where it is executed and shall be signed by the official(s) whose signature and authority shall be verified) Appendix–G Certificate of Local Content &lt;Certificate from the statutory auditor or cost auditor of the company (in case of companies) or from a practicing cost accountant or practicing chartered accountant (in respect of suppliers other than companies) giving the percentage of local content, on their letter head with Registration Number with seal.&gt; Date: To, ______________________ ______________________ ______________________ Dear Sir, Ref.: RFP No. : ____________ Dated: _________ This is to certify that proposed ______________ &lt;details of services&gt; is having the local content of ___________ % as defined in the above mentioned RFP.</content><clause id="clause-25" level="7" numbering="2."><content>This certificate is submitted in reference to the Public Procurement (Preference to Make in India), Order 2017 including revision thereto. Signature of Statutory Auditor/Cost Auditor Registration Number: Seal Counter-signed: Bidder OEM &lt; Certified copy of board resolution for appointment of statutory/cost auditor should also be enclosed with the certificate of local content.&gt; OR Format for Self-Certification of Local Content Date: To, ______________________ ______________________ ______________________ Dear Sir, Ref.: RFP No. : ____________ Dated: _________ This is to certify that proposed ______________ &lt; details of services &gt; is having the local content of ___________ % as defined in the above mentioned RFP.</content></clause></clause></clause></clause></clause></clause><clause id="clause-26" level="2" numbering="1."><content>The details of location(s) at which the local value addition is made are as under: Sl No Product details Name of place 1 2</content><clause id="clause-27" level="3" numbering="3."><content>This certificate is submitted in reference to the Public Procurement (Preference to Make in India), Order 2017 including revision thereto. Signature of authorised official Name: Company seal:</content></clause></clause></clause></document>
